<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Hilton Worldwide Global Media Center &gt; Financial  News</title>
    <link>http://news.hiltonworldwide.com/index.cfm/newsroom/category/topic/1149</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2014 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description />
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright 2014 Hilton Worldwide Global Media Center</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2014 05:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hilton Worldwide Agrees to Sell the Waldorf Astoria New York to Anbang Insurance Group Co. Ltd. for $1.95 Billion</title>
      <link>http://news.hiltonworldwide.com/index.cfm/newsroom/detail/27488</link>
      <description>Hilton Worldwide Holdings Inc. (“Hilton Worldwide”) today announced it has entered into an agreement with Anbang Insurance Group Co. Ltd. (“Anbang”), under which Anbang has agreed to purchase the Waldorf Astoria New York for $1.95 billion. </description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2014 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1149-27488</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hilton Worldwide Announces Third Quarter 2014 Earnings Release Date</title>
      <link>http://news.hiltonworldwide.com/index.cfm/newsroom/detail/27483</link>
      <description>Hilton Worldwide Holdings Inc. (NYSE: HLT) will report third quarter 2014 financial results prior to the stock market open on Friday, October 31, 2014, followed by a conference call at 10:00 a.m. Eastern Time. Christopher J. Nassetta, Hilton Worldwide&apos;s president and chief executive officer, and Kevin Jacobs, Hilton Worldwide&apos;s executive vice president and chief financial officer, will discuss the company&apos;s performance and lead a question-and-answer session.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2014 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1149-27483</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hilton Worldwide Reports Strong Second Quarter 2014 Results, Exceeding EPS and RevPAR Expectations; Raises Full Year Outlook</title>
      <link>http://news.hiltonworldwide.com/index.cfm/newsroom/detail/27215</link>
      <description> Hilton Worldwide Holdings Inc. (&quot;Hilton,&quot; &quot;Hilton Worldwide&quot; or the &quot;Company&quot;) (NYSE: HLT) today reported its second quarter 2014 results and raised its full year 2014 outlook.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2014 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1149-27215</guid>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
